cepro.com 2019-09-20

# Privacy Policy - CE Pro

### Emerald Expositions is a leading owner and operator of business-to-business tradeshows in the United States connecting hundreds of thousands of buyers and sellers across multiple diversified end markets. Emerald Expositions owns and/or operates multiple trade shows, publications, conferences and websites serving various industries.

**EFFECTIVE DATE: May 25, 2018**

**Privacy Policy**

This privacy policy covers the collection and use of information for this website and any websites or mobile applications that link to it, as well as the information we collect when you interact with us through social media or other websites and online services (in each instance a “website”). This website is managed and operated by Emerald Expositions, LLC (“Emerald Expositions” or “us” or “we”).

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (“EEA”) or Switzerland, please see “Users in the EEA and Switzerland” at the end of this Privacy Policy.

**About Emerald Expositions**

Emerald Expositions is a leading owner and operator of business-to-business tradeshows in the United States connecting hundreds of thousands of buyers and sellers across multiple diversified end markets. Emerald Expositions owns and/or operates multiple trade shows, publications, conferences and websites serving various industries. For more information please visit [www.emeraldexpositions.com](https://www.emeraldexpo.com/).

**What Information We Collect**

Information you give us: We collect information that you choose to provide to us when you register for a trade show, conference or other event; purchase trade show, conference or other event-related services; subscribe to our magazines (either directly or through another company such as a subscription agency); sign up for email newsletters; enter a sweepstakes or contest; participate in surveys; or otherwise submit through our website. During the registration process we may request certain contact information and demographic information about you such as your name, mailing address, email address, company name, size of company and title. We also may receive information about you from other sources and add it to the information you have provided to us. If you choose to register for a trade show, conference or other event on this website, you may also be asked to provide your credit card information to fulfill your registration request.

Information collected automatically: Like most other websites, we may automatically collect information and data through the use of log files, “cookies” or other information storage and tracking technology. These technologies allow us to track usage behavior and compile website usage information that will allow for the improvement of content and targeting advertising. This information may include your internet protocol (IP) address, associated company name, if any, browser type, platform, internet service provider (ISP), time and date stamp, general geographic information, referring pages and exit pages.

Our websites incorporate tracking technologies managed by Google, Facebook, and Twitter, all of which have their own privacy policies. To learn more about their services, and to opt-out of their tracking, please visit the following resources:

Google Analytics: <https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites>

Facebook: <https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217>

Twitter: <https://help.twitter.com/en/rules-and-policies/twitter-cookies>

**How We Use and Disclose Information**

Emerald Expositions may use and disclose your contact information for any of the following reasons:

To provide, maintain, personalize, optimize, and improve the website, including research and analytics regarding use of the website, or to remember you when you leave and return to the website;

To provide and improve our products and services, to process any transactions you request, or authenticate you as a customer;

To deliver advertising, including interest-based advertising on our websites and other websites and applications;

To provide you with information about products or services you are interested in, including trade shows, conferences and other events;

To provide you with e-newsletters you have requested;

To send you notices for subscription renewal; and

To contact you regarding marketing endeavors.

From time to time, Emerald Expositions may also share your contact information with other organizations, such as trade show exhibitors and vendors, for marketing purposes. If you do not wish to receive such offers, please refer to the “Contact” section below.

We contract with third party companies that we have engaged to provide us with specialized services, including, but not limited to, customer service, registration, subscription fulfillment, housing, booth decoration, freight services, research, statistical analysis, application development, list cleansing, postal mailings, email and fax deployment, and other information services. These companies or individuals may be provided with access to information about you, but only as needed to perform their functions. These companies are required to maintain the confidentiality, security and integrity of such information.

Notwithstanding any other provision of this privacy policy, we may disclose information about you to any third party when disclosure is required by law, or desirable to permit us to exercise or preserve our legal rights or take action regarding potentially illegal activities or to protect the safety of any person. In the event we are acquired by or merged with a third-party entity or in the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information we have collected as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control.

**Interest-Based Advertising**

We and our partners use cookies, web beacons or other technologies to collect information from our website. These companies may use information about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on this website and other websites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. They may also collect information about your online activities over time and across different websites and other online services. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please visit the Network Advertising Initiative ([http://optout.networkadvertising.org](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/)) and Digital Advertising Alliance ([http://optout.aboutads.info](http://optout.aboutads.info/)).

Your browser or device may include “Do Not Track” functionality. The information collection and disclosure practices and the choices that we provide to you will continue to operate as described in this privacy policy, whether or not a Do Not Track signal is received.

We may combine information you give us or that we collect automatically with our business records, information from third parties, or information collected from another browser or device to personalize our communications with you and to deliver better advertising.

**Children**

This website is not directed at children under the age of 13 and does not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian believes that this website has collected the personal information of a child under the age of 13, please contact [privacy@emeraldexpo.com](mailto:privacy@emeraldexpo.com?subject=Child%20Under%2013).

**Data Storage, Transfers, and Security**

We may store the personal details we hold about you for as long as we have a legitimate business need. We may store this information in the United States or we may transfer it to any other country. If you are located outside of the United States and voluntarily submit information to us, we may transfer that information to and store that information in the United States. The data protection laws in countries to which personal data are transferred may or may not provide a level of protection equivalent to the laws in your home country. Wherever we hold the data, we will apply the terms of this privacy policy and any applicable data protection law. We maintain certain procedures to protect the confidentiality, security and integrity of information you submit to us or that we collect while it is controlled by us. However, the storage and communication of such information cannot always be completely secure. Also, we cannot and do not guarantee that data transferred to third parties in accordance with this privacy policy will be protected against intentional or accidental misuse or loss.

**California Residents**

California law permits California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of your personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to [privacy@emeraldexpo.com](mailto:privacy@emeraldexpo.com?subject=California%20Customer%20Choice%20Notice) specifying that you seek your “California Customer Choice Notice” in the subject line.

**Users in the EEA and Switzerland**

If you are a resident of the EEA or Switzerland, the following information applies with respect to personal data collected through your use of our website.

Purposes of processing and legal basis for processing: We process personal data consistent with our disclosures in this privacy policy. We process personal data on the following legal bases: (1) with your consent; (2) as necessary to perform our agreement to provide our websites and services related to our websites; and (3) as necessary for our legitimate interests in providing the website and services related to the website where those interests do not override your fundamental rights and freedoms related to data privacy.

Transfers: Personal data we collect may be transferred to, and stored and processed in, the United States or any other country in which we or our affiliates or processors maintain facilities. We will ensure that transfers of personal data to a third country or an international organization are subject to appropriate safeguards.

Individual Rights: If you are a resident of the EEA or Switzerland, we respect your rights according to Chapter 3 of the EU General Data Protection Regulation. In order to verify your identity, we may require you to provide us with personal information prior to accessing any records containing information about you. Please contact us using the information below.

Visit the [Cookie Declaration page](https://www.cepro.com/cookie-declaration/) to change or remove your consent.

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**

We may change this privacy policy and our data collection and management practices. We reserve the right to update changes to this privacy policy and to our practices in collecting and handling personal information. If we make material changes, we will post a notice at this website and indicate at the top of this statement when it was most recently updated.

**Contact**

Please contact us if you have questions or wish to take any action with respect to information to which this privacy policy applies. You can reach us by sending an email to [privacy@emeraldexpo.com](mailto:privacy@emeraldexpo.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy%20Inquiry).

If you do not wish to receive marketing information from Emerald Expositions, or wish to opt out of future email promotions from Emerald Expositions, please email [:privacy@emeraldexpo.com](mailto:privacy@emeraldexpo.com?subject=Opt-Out). Please note that all promotional email messages you receive from Emerald Expositions will include an option to opt out of future email communications.
